(Sheldon:)...and I was afraid if we ran into them
on the way out, I'd be obligated to do so.
(Bernadette:)I'm so disappointed
it didn't work with him and Penny.
(Amy:)Me too. Out of deference to them,
Iet's not flaunt our happy relationship.
(Sheldon:)You have a keen insight into
the human heart, Amy Farrah Fowler.
We are next to a Subaru
with a Gore-Lieberman bumper sticker.
Well, I doubt they'd wanna
talk about that, so we're fine.
(Howard:)I'm surprised to see you here
after it went so badly with Penny.
(Leonard:)Well, hey, we're grown-ups.
We can still be friends.
(Bernadette:)Boy, I don't know if I could be friends
with Howie if we broke up.
- Why not?
- I'm a very vengeful person.
- Really?
- With access to weaponized smallpox.
Let me get you some water. You need
menus, or you know what you want?
(Howard:)Leonard knows what he wants, but it
Iooks like he's not gonna get it from you.